[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Mr. Fang, I'm hungry and sleepy right now.
Do you think it'll eat us?
Either it eats us
and turns us into poop,
or we eat this poop monster
and turn it into poop.
Mom!
Come here, come here!
Mr. Fang, I'm done for!
Go get another torch!
Bie Fan, go!
Mr. Fang! Mom!
Go!
Mr. Fang!
Bie Fan, you...
Want some grilled snake? Grilled snake.
Mr. Fang.
It's pretty strong!
Mr. Fang, grab its neck!
It's so long, where's its neck?
It's so long! Which part is its neck?
Bie Fan, Bie Fan! Hit its weak spot!
Mr. Fang!
Bite it!
Mr. Fang
Mr. Fang, why isn't it moving?
You...
You wait here.
I'll go take a look.
It's dead.
R-Really?
Then h-how did it die?
I... I know. I know now.
Mr. Fang, it died of frustration.
Look inside its mouth,
it's propped open by a stick.
It doesn't have hands,
so it couldn't pull the stick out.
So it must've died of frustration.
This snake had a huge temper.
You killed a python!
That's amazing!
You're amazing!
Original! Original! Original!
Then we're both amazing!
We killed a python together!
Mom! Mom!
We won't get eaten by it!
We can eat it instead!
That's too fast!
Just spin it faster and you're good.
Should I put it all in?
Just half is fine.
You're the chef.
Will this even taste good, Mr. Fang?
It's good.
I can't get it out.
Here.
Thanks.
That was delicious.
Maybe this meal
is the most delicious meal I've ever had in my life.
What do we call this?
This is Rock-Bottom Hotpot.
And we don't even have to wait for a table.
It's not bad.
I think that hotpot soup base was a bit salty.
When we get out of here,
I'll make some hotpot base for you to try.
You know how to make hotpot base?
I... I'm a chef.
Sichuan cuisine, Cantonese... I can cook anything.
Then what do you think is
the best meal you've ever had in your life?
Mapo Tofu.
What's so good about Mapo Tofu?
Let me tell you,
I had the honor
of eating Buddha Jumps Over the Wall once.
It was incredibly delicious.
Mixed with rice, it was absolutely amazing.
Mapo Tofu mixed with rice is also delicious.
One is tofu.
The other is abalone.
One is home-style.
The other is a famous delicacy.
In terms of their level and price,
they're completely different.
How can you even compare them?
Mapo Tofu tastes better!
Buddha Jumps Over the Wall tastes better!
Why are you so stubborn?
Why are you so stubborn? I...
All the energy I got from that snake went into arguing with you!
Why are you so stubborn?
Tell me, what makes Mapo Tofu so good?
Come on, let's hear it.
Mapo Tofu.
First, add a decent amount of oil to the wok.
Peanut oil is the best.
Peanut oil is fragrant.
Once the oil is hot, add the minced meat.
Once the minced meat changes color,
add a spoonful of cooking wine to remove the raw smell.
When the minced meat is fried golden brown,
then add two spoonfuls of broad bean paste.
Remember, Bie Fan,
it's two spoonfuls.
Too much, and it'll be too salty.
After frying the bean paste until the red oil comes out,
add the chilies and minced garlic.
Then add some water,
light soy sauce, dark soy sauce, and the tofu.
Add a bit more water.
After simmering on low heat for five minutes,
we add it in two batches...
Two batches.
Cornstarch slurry. One spoonful.
Two spoonfuls. Good.
Right before taking it out of the wok,
add a little chili powder.
And a bit of chopped green onion.
See? Did you get all that?
The Mapo Tofu my mom makes
is the best in the world.
I think you're right.
This Mapo Tofu
must taste better than Buddha Jumps Over the Wall.
Yeah.
Bie Fan, what's your lifelong wish?
I want to take a shower.
I haven't showered for days.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I want to take a shower too.
We stink. This smell.
I mean, do you have any bigger wishes?
I want to take a bath.
Does it have to be about personal hygiene?
I... I mean, like...
just...
like, in your whole life,
the thing you want to do most.
Watch the flag-raising ceremony at Tiananmen.
That's a good wish.
Just watch the flag-raising?
I haven't thought about anything else yet.
Mr. Fang,
in your life so far,
is there something you've always wanted to do?
Me?
Have everyone read my poetry collection.
And then?
Then the collection becomes a bestseller.
Selling 100 million copies.
And then what?
There's an "and then"?
This conversation is getting fun.
The book has already sold 100 million copies.
Shouldn't we have some ambition?
Then,
my poetry collection
gets rated on the platforms,
and it has to be over a 9.
But not a perfect 10.
A perfect 10 means no room to grow,
no room to progress either.
Then everyone's comments below would be,
"This Fang Haowen is so talented.
We totally misjudged him before.
A masterpiece!"
And then what?
And then...
And then, I'd have to...
win the Nobel Prize in Literature, of course!
But this Nobel Prize in Literature,
shouldn't be too easy to win.
It has to carry weight.
For example, the people competing with me
must all be big shots.
Like, for instance,
you know, what's his name...
Mo Yan,
Haruki Murakami,
Yu Hua.
When the time comes,
we'll all be at the award ceremony.
We'll all be sitting in the audience,
sitting in a row,
in suits and ties,
looking totally sharp.
And then,
feeling extremely nervous,
not knowing who will finally win.
Suddenly, my name is announced.
My expression then: shocked!
Then confident.
Winning is a sure thing.
And after winning the prize?
After winning?
After winning...
I'll walk right up to Jin Furong.
I'll walk up to the people who insulted me.
I'll walk up to the people who sold me out.
I'll walk up to the people who exploited me.
Then I'll hold up my trophy,
and I'll ask them...
I'll say, "Am I
truly talented or not?"
And they'll say yes.
And then?
And then...
I'll just forgive them.
Then you'll be happy.
Can I get a refill?
Sure.
Thanks.
Once we get out of here,
make me some Mapo Tofu.
I'll take you to watch the flag raising.
Here.
Thanks.
So when are we getting out?
That massive chunk of old snake meat
is enough to feed us for months.
Maybe we'll get out tomorrow.
It's been two months.
In a huge forest full of wild beasts,
the chances of survival are really slim.
It's only been two months.
Just two months, that's all.
We confirmed it last time,
they're somewhere in this forest.
We just need to keep looking!
We have to find them, dead or alive.
Let's go look for them again!
Mr. Rong,
over the past few months,
the police have invested
a massive amount of resources
into searching for Fang Haowen and Bie Fan.
Right now, there really are no useful leads.
The investigation has hit a dead end.
Based on standard procedures and overall schedules,
our search operations
will have to be suspended for now.
If there are any new developments,
we will notify you immediately.
We ask for your understanding.
Bie Fan!
Bie Fan
The sun is out.
Time to get some sun.
Coming.
Mr. Fang.
We only have so much time each day.
Where was I? Right.
Chapter 53.
It says Tang Sanzang and his three disciples
arrived at Xiliang Women's Kingdom.
Tang Sanzang and Zhu Bajie were thirsty,
and wanted some water.
So they drank from the Pregnancy River.
Guess what happened?
Their stomachs started hurting.
You might think,
they needed to poop.
Nope.
Drinking from the Pregnancy River makes you pregnant.
You have to give birth.
Drink the water and you get pregnant?
And have to give birth?
Bie Fan, have you never dated anyone?
I'm still young.
I haven't thought about that yet.
We never talked about this before.
Now we've got something to talk about today.
Let me ask you.
Have you never had that kind of urge?
What urge?
The urge to get married and have kids.
Do I have to get married and have kids?
That's life. It's a path we all take.
That-that-that's what makes it perfect.
I don't want to have kids.
Why?
I don't want my child
to be as unhealthy as me.
Who said that?
My classmate.
They said I'm a big idiot,
that my dad's a big idiot,
and my child will be a big idiot too.
Tell me who said that once we get out.
I'll beat him up.
Let me tell you,
if anyone dares call you an idiot again,
I'll be the first to teach them a lesson.
Do you believe me?
You've lied to me before.
I, Fang Haowen, swear to God,
I'll never lie to you again in my life.
And I'm telling you very seriously,
you're not an idiot at all.
And you're perfectly healthy.
Mr... Mr. Fang.
Thank you.
If anyone calls you a big idiot in the future,
I'll beat them up too.
Tell you what, listen to me.
First, don't learn to swear like me.
Second,
no one will ever call me a big idiot.
Hard to say.
Mr. Fang, what are you doing?
Don't just stand there! Hurry up!
Bring all those bricks over here!
You just said you wouldn't call me an idiot!
You're not an idiot! You're not! You're not!
Hurry up, hurry up! You're so smart!
Hurry up, genius! Quick, quick, quick!
Like this?
Take the bed apart!
We're just a little bit short.
Listen,
once we reach this vine, we'll be set.
We'll be out of here.
Really?
Step on my shoulders.
I'll boost you up.
Grab the vine.
Mr. Fang.
I... I'm scared.
You're a grown man.
What's there to be afraid of?
We're just one step away.
Get up here!
It's too high, Mr. Fang. I'm scared.
Trust me.
Can you reach it?
I can't, Mr. Fang.
Bie Fan.
Just trust me.
I'll count to three, then jump.
Grab the vine and we're set.
One, two, go!
Did you get it?
Mr. Fang, I got it!
Are you cold?
I'm cold.
Let me add some wood.
I'm still cold, Mr. Fang.
Still cold? Let me add some more.
I'm cold, Mr. Fang.
Mr. Fang, it hurts.
Just bear with it.
Let me see if it's any better.
I think... it's a little infected.
What should we do then?
It's best if we go to a hospital.
We can't get out.
I... I'll add some more firewood.
Mr. Fang
Don't burn it. It's the book you gave me.
It's fine.
I'll give you another copy later.
Mr. Fang
Wait for me!
Don't fall asleep!
Bie Fan.
Wait for me to come back and save you.
Don't fall asleep.
The three elements of success are
persistence, control, and acceptance.
What is Success?
Page 69.
Persistence.
Persistence is also an essential virtue for success.
As long as you persist in doing one thing well,
success will get closer and closer to you.
Success requires seeing things through.
Success means never giving up halfway.
Never giving up halfway.
Please believe in the power of belief.
You have to believe
that you will get better and better.
You must believe
that many beautiful things in the future
will happen.
As long as you believe,
all your troubles
will leave you.
All your pain will be easily resolved,
and only then will health and happiness
stay by your side.
You must maintain
an optimistic mood
and a positive mindset.
You must use
a kind perspective to view yourself.
To view yourself.
You must believe
the more optimistic,
the more positive,
the more at peace,
the luckier you will be.
What you're experiencing now
is nothing but before the dawn...
the brief darkness before the dawn.
The brief darkness.
Life
isn't always what it appears to be.
It's not what it appears to be.
It requires you to go step by step,
facing the wind,
braving the rain,
tasting all the bitterness in the world,
only to realize
only to realize that impermanence is the only constant.
Success
is breathing fresh air.
Mr. Fang, I really can't think of anything.
You useless idiot! So stupid.
What's so hard about thinking of a poem?
Just say whatever comes to mind!
Just say anything. Come on.
I can't just say anything. Go back, go back.
Go back. You useless idiot.
So useless.
You little failure.
You useless piece of trash.
Writing poetry is very simple.
Just write whatever comes to mind.
Go for it.
"Friend."
By Bie Fan.
Rong Sihai is my friend.
Fang Haowen is also my friend.
I'm very happy.
Very, very, very good!
What book are you reading?
"I Have 'No' Talent."
By Fang Haowen.
I haven't even published it yet!
Tomorrow, Huanxi City will hold
a grand Fang Haowen
memorial service.
I know you're gone,
but I still
can't believe it's true.
Wait a minute.
What's your relationship to the deceased?
Go on in.
I am the deceased.